A Guide to the Dan H. Pletta Papers, 1958-1994
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Box 13
  - How to Balance the Pros and Cons of Technology. (Box-folder 13-609)
  - Chinese Education, Correspondence, and Cards. (Box-folder 13-610)
  - China, Correspondence. (Box-folder 13-611)
  - Chinese Education. (Box-folder 13-612)
  - China, Postcards, Brochures, Orville Schell New Yorker article, 1984. (Box-folder 13-613)
  - Volume One (Box-folder 13-614)
  - Professionalism and Ethics (Volume 2). (Box-folder 13-615)
  - Engineering Science Mechanics, Materials Testing Laboratory Manual. (Box-folder 13-616)
  - Department of Engineering Science and Mechanics Administration & Regulations. (Box-folder 13-617)
- Box 14
  - ASCE Committee on Society Objectives Planning and Organization (COSOPO), 1970-1972. (Box-folder 14-618)
  - ASCE - PAC & CSPO, 1971. (Box-folder 14-619)
  - Lobbying - Highway Trucks - Covers to 1982. (Box-folder 14-620)
  - Professional Programs. (Box-folder 14-621)
  - Papers on "Dependence of Technological Progress on Industrial Development & Professional Advocacy." (Box-folder 14-622)
  - Articles and Notes. (Box-folder 14-623)
  - News Item - Six-year degree. (Box-folder 14-624)
  - ASEE Outstanding Engineering Educators - April 4-6, 1993, Nashville - SE Section Meeting. (Box-folder 14-625)
  - Lox Storage Tanks. (Box-folder 14-626)
  - Professional Activities Committee, 1969-1972. (Box-folder 14-627)
  - Foreign Contacts. (Box-folder 14-628)
  - Professional Obligations. (Box-folder 14-629)
  - University Club Housing and Building Committee. (Box-folder 14-630)
  - University Club Renovation. (Box-folder 14-631)
  - University Club - Miscellaneous & Correspondence. (Box-folder 14-632)
  - University Club Fund Raising. (Box-folder 14-633)
  - India. (Box-folder 14-634)
  - President's Symposium: Ethics and the Professions. (Box-folder 14-635)
  - Applied Mechanics. (Box-folder 14-636)
  - EM 511 - Non Planar Rings. (Box-folder 14-637)
  - "The Professional Need to Guide Technology." (Box-folder 14-638)
  - University of Texas, Civil Engineering Education Conferences, 1994-1995. (Box-folder 14-639)
  - Miscellaneous Articles, Correspondence, Notes. (Box-folder 14-640)
  - Miscellaneous Articles, Correspondence, Notes. (Box-folder 14-641)
  - Report on the Failure of the Tool Joints for William T. Burton Industries. (Box-folder 14-642)
  - Virginia Steel Company, Open Web Joists. (Box-folder 14-643)
  - Virginia Steel Company. (Box-folder 14-644)
  - Virginia Steel Company, Long Span Open Web Joists. (Box-folder 14-645)
  - WAFCO, Inc., Multicellular Tetrahedral Bar. (Box-folder 14-646)
  - Revision of The Engineering Profession, Charles H. Samson. (Box-folder 14-647)
  - Tall Tales of Blacksburg. (Box-folder 14-648)
  - The Engineer's Expanding Destiny. (Box-folder 14-649)
  - Volume Three. (Box-folder 14-650)
  - Volume Four, Engineering Education at Virginia Tech. (Box-folder 14-651)
  - Nature of Engineering Course, Spring 1980. (Box-folder 14-652)
  - Illinois Institute of Technology Pamphlets on Ethics. (Box-folder 14-653)
  - Interdisciplinary Safeguards and Professional Unity, Michael Duncan, Correspondence. (Box-folder 14-654)
  - National Institute of Engineering Ethics, Engineering Ethics Update. (Box-folder 14-655)
  - Professional Engineering Unity. (Box-folder 14-656)
  - Six-year Practice-Oriented Degree. (Box-folder 14-657)
  - Film - "Ethics on Trial," 1991-92; Worldwatch Seminar. (Box-folder 14-658)
  - ASCE. (Box-folder 14-659)
  - Virginia Commission on Government Accountability and Ethics. (Box-folder 14-660)
  - Slide Notes. (Box-folder 14-661)
- Box 15
  - Glass Slides: General Motors Photographic Department.
  - Slides (2 boxes): history of engineering, unity, landmarks of places traveled; construction sites, misc.
  - Videotapes: "Ethics on Trial" (part 1 and 2); Whistleblowing and the APO.
  - Instruments: slide rule, circular measuring tool, pressure converter.
- Box 16
  - Certificates and Awards